MUHAMMAD HAMZA IMRAN

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



0346-6248668



hamzaimraan0@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/mhamzaimran

PROFILE

Passionate Software Engineer from NUST with 2+ years of experience in designing and developing mobile applications. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies. Able to work independently of remote locations or in office environments as needed by the company.

SKILLS

- Mobile App Development
- Figma/AdobeXD
- · Logic Building
- Creating Thinking
- Database Implementation
- Problem-Solving
- Project Management
- Object Oriented Programming
- Clean Coding

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Superior College

2016 - 2018

BACHELOR OF SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

NUST H-12 Islabamad

2019 - 2023

EXPERIENCE

FLUTTER INTERN

Goprogs Technologies Pvt Ltd

Nov 2022 - Present

- Front-end Mobile Application Development
- Logic Building for improving User Interaction Experience
- · API integration into mobile front-end
- Cross-platform Applications building and fixing bugs

MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPER INTERN

AS-Siraat

Sept 2022 - Dec 2022

- Mobile Application UI Designing using Figma Tool
- Building App Front-end with given design
- Local Database Implementation to improve performance
- Defining User Journey and Improving Experience

TASK MANAGENET PROJECT

Semester Project

Apr 2022 - May 2022

- Database administration and mobile design
- Cross Platform to-do list app with database management
- Logic Building for multiple themes for user experience
- CRUD operations for task handling